[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1871 what major Midwest city burned down in a fire that was deemed one of the largest disasters in the United States?", "correct_answer": "Chicago", "incorrect_answers": ["Cleveland", "Detroit", "St. Louis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Peanuts are not considered to be nuts. They are legumes, and belong to the same class as peas and beans.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This person was the first African-American to hit a home run in Major League Baseball.", "correct_answer": "Dan Bankhead", "incorrect_answers": ["Larry Doby", "Jackie Robinson", "Monte Irvin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What educational, non-fiction full length animated film was released in 1957?", "correct_answer": "Hemo the Magnificent", "incorrect_answers": ["Inside the Atom", "Young Abe", "George Washington and the Revolution"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Butterflies taste their food through this organ.", "correct_answer": "The legs", "incorrect_answers": ["The wings", "Their faceted eyes", "The proboscis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This primitive shark, with a brown thin eel-like body, has six pairs of gill slits and trident-like teeth.", "correct_answer": "Frilled shark", "incorrect_answers": ["Tiger shark", "Bull shark", "Sharpnose seven-gill shark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of weather pattern on Mars can obscure the surface from view?", "correct_answer": "Dust Storms", "incorrect_answers": ["Thunder Storms", "Hurricanes", "Snow Storms"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Windows Vista commercials have boasted of the Record Live Television capability of the operating system. What is necessary to use this function?", "correct_answer": "TV Tuner Card", "incorrect_answers": ["Optical Drive", "Cable Box", "Digital Television"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During the last period of the pregnancy, the fetus drops towards the opening of the pelvis and this part of the body changes its shape.", "correct_answer": "The abdomen", "incorrect_answers": ["The hips", "The breasts", "The uterus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What legendary American frontiersman commanded a major fort in Colorado?", "correct_answer": "Kit Carson", "incorrect_answers": ["Daniel Boone", "Wild Bill Cody", "Jim Bowie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The eyes of males are bigger than those of females.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these characteristics is generally associated with carnivorous animals, particularly predators?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Aggressive behavior", "Claws", "Sharp teeth"]}]